we’ve worked out a semblance of something like that, we’re
мы чему сработано подобие так мы народ
such a people they sit for a
такой они сидят на
period of nowhere
период никуда
good from Poland and Ukraine
добрый из польши и украины
didn’t show after the Russians
не показала после россиян
threw out Poland and
выкинул польше а
you choose the region, well, Russia, and I put it, I
ты выбирай край ну россия а я ставила я
don’t know what mono food for
не знаю чему в моно пищу
me is the
мне
address by location, okay, punching from the
адрес по локации да ладно пробивая от
most from  Ukraine until because of the printout,
самого из украины до из-за распечатки
chipped or yes, it fit in,
скол или да про вместилось
and I’m the boss, a student from the cooler,
а я начальница студентка из кулирка у
we have online, at school, the doctors, the student,
нас онлайн ну школы врачи студент
didn’t know the advertiser
не ведал рекламиста
Kharkiv about the damn hapkido inflated 13
харьков о блин хапкидо раздувал 13
ferrets, the arches drove us scared, we are
хорьки арки поехала на нам страшно мы
there, so it’s scary saltovka,
там поэтому страшно салтовка
we are developed, we are paired with Kharkov  she
мы развитые мы паре с харьковом она
flew strictly on this conveniently there,
строго на этом прилетал удобно там
they say, and there were a bunch of people in sparks, in
дескать и стояла куча людей в искорки по
fact, not the world, I’m at once in Poland, it’s
сути не миру я зараз польши
normal
нормально
for the centuries, our primals are picked up,
места век прималы наших подобран
these friends are in the torment of fright again,
делает эти друзья на муку испуга снова
there are Poles in this, not bone hatred,
там поляки в этом не костко ненависти
grandson, I don’t know,
внук я не знаю
and due to the tekke shocker  I’ll pick you up with a
причем за счет текке шокером стук вас с
man in the wind and now I
человеком соберу in the wind и вот я
’ll always be in Europe, looking for something wrong and
всегда буду в европе глядь чем не то и
potency
потенция
you are on lined out of your choose the
вы на выложены из своих выбрать
settings there is muhosranske t  so here are
настройки есть мухосранске так и вот
the vinsadas and how can you talk
винсады и как же ты бы побачим можно в
about people you don’t care bread you
отношении людей это ты ничего хлеб ты
stayed from Kharkov there lived for rent in
побыла с харькова там пожила напрокат в
Poland there prices are there for a tribute
польше там цены то что там на дань
tourists in the same place a month on the wire the state
туристы там же месяц на проводе штат
or who I respect Yura podsak rut
либо кто я ты уважаешь юра подсак рут
very much  arni garni of love and give it was I
очень арни гарни любви и дать ему было я
published about the outskirts of the duzhe garne people are just
издал об окраинам дуже гарне люди просто
near russia i chu vladi china however hall
у россии я чу влади china однако зала а
why do we need your europe here we are there in
зачем нам это ваши европа вот мы там в
turkey and
турции и
well and sho punish him we have
ну и шо его накажи у нас в европу ездят
only those who go to europe  money that
только те у кого есть деньги которые
deceived the authorities and somehow it
обманули власть и так-то оно само собой
pierced by itself and said very smart in May,
пронзила и сказал очень умных на мая
good Ukraine and
хорошие украине и
moreover, they came in and no matter where you start
причем зашли и бы вы ни там начинает
where you go Europe will not become richer alive
куда ты ходишь европа живым богаче не
Russia will punish so Europe live
стану россии в накажет так европа живой
luggage and not from Ukraine these are Jamaicans  the abyss
багаж и не из украины это ямайцы бездны
and we
и мы
have ours there with such there to cook f4
у наших там при таких там готовить f4
it’s so in it I seem like a megami player we
это так в ней кажусь megami игрок мы
want the euro because it’s
хотим евро потому что там офигенно там
awesome there Krasinets we have Thai integral powder
красинец у нас пудра интеграла тайской
just and in Moscow they have these icons of their not
просто а москве у них эти иконы их не
indigenous becoming sitting and still living in
коренные став сидит и живут до сих
Europe h  ate Europe but your own mana Navarin
европе чате европе но свой маны наварин
our us ty Pindos he was Anglo-Saxons, then
нашу нам ти [__] он был англосаксы то
you don’t know why you’ll run out of steam faster than this,
вы не знаешь мы почему же ты краще этому
organize their tasbih better
выдохнемся их тасбих организовать краще
and here are the standard beacons, but you don’t live
и вот и маяки стандарт а вот вы не живут
in magnesium, don’t want the strength of your notes
в магнии не хочет силы своих нотки
, people are happy with these words  punish
приносят люди довольный эти слова накажи
what
чего
else we can develop our vlad we
еще мы можем разработать наши владом мы
can’t forget anything so you 2 notebook of
ничего не можем забыть так вы 2 тетрадь
emotions the president supposedly give you a vegetable
эмоций президент вас якобы дать овощ
would you like to choose and what are we with an
хотела бы ты выбрал был и мы чему с
ajax rob like nets we would be
робом аякса наподобие сеток бы мы народ
such a people and over there and sit on the ass jealous
такой а вон и сидеть на жопе ревную
michigan and shy  don’t pull us anywhere,
мичиган и роблять никуда не дергайте
but you can still goat you’re here a lot at a
нами но еще можно коза ты здесь много за
time, maybe both in the end, there was enough
раз на может оба в итоге на хватило
Izar with your own, maybe everything means say to
изара своими может и все значит скажи к
business, I was scared with a Belarusian, I killed
бизнесу я с белорусом испугался убил
Ruse pshada, the sewn president of Belarus when
русе пшада вшитой президент беларуси при
hiring, you really will come out, you don’t seem to
найме вы правда выйдет вы не кажет мы
mind who we are  - something in it is clearly under these
против кто-то в нем четко под эти
coins with an icon of peppers like but we ca
монетки значком перцы типа но мы ничего
n’t do anything on the back, here’s what you’re
не можем на обороте вот на что то вы про
doing right about the president, but it’s like your
правильно делает президент а вроде ваш
tank is over the baht and screaming starts
танк это над бат и кричит начинается вот
here and  Belarusians of mana can’t forget anything of the
тут а белорусы маны не может ничего
moon at least on Peter’s face like
забыто луны хоть на петр ему лица вот
this verbally ati so he starts Peter to
так вербально ati вот он и начинает петр
them so you can’t at least
им так что ты не можешь так то хотя бы
drink your visually Belarus from
напиток своих зрительно беларуси из
Russia and Russians to herself she’s on the right for
россии и россиян к самой она справа за
her president of Ukraine wash away and
своего президента украины смоем и
Ukrainian  the core of the winter for the whole naumovna
украинским ядро зиму по целой наумовна
borussia price and the Belarusian so it seems, but the
боруссия цену и белоруска так уж кажет а
account of our president
счет наш президент
from inter, even in harp, the ukrainian
от интера еще в харпе украинскому
was afraid not of the russian lagman, just a
испугалась не российского лагмана просто
dad to sleep and ukrainian to this, i want
батько спать и украинскую этому я хочу и
russian ukraine, well, it’s just that kharkov is
российской украине ну просто так харьков
more mica ukrainian to understand aliska
больше слюда украинскую разуметь алиску
qualys so
qualys так
very much  or surzhik all inside the
очень много или суржик all inside the
slobozhanshchina c shuklin skipping with an element
слобожанщина c шуклин скипать элементом
biting their people speak ukrainian and
кусал их люди говорить украинскую а
when i come to the park to crap it was still done
приезжаю в парке в обосрусь еще велась
so at a time it can change the handles after c
так за раз может ручки изменится после c
hatchback from friends
hatchback из друзей
it turned out to be a
так вышло-то
ukrainian mova and then it happened and
украинскую мову а тут и так сталося а
you get a grasp of the miniver article  on whom,
вы вчитайтесь минивер стати на кого
which masonry is cool on them, but
который кладочку прикольно на них а а
I’m all there for a couple of months, they rubbed Chinese,
я все там пару месяцев китайской втирали
saved yours for
сэкономили ваш к песчаным
sandy days  the ninth hour until
девятый час до
everything go on your glory ukraine
все давай дальше свое слава украине
vodka happens cool moments yes right now I'll
водки бывает прикольные моменты да я щас
try to get the Russians poland
россиян попытаюсь добиться польша
valgrind sugar until fate forgive me the
valgrind сахар до судьба что простите
charisma of height 6 russian
совсем харизму высоты 6 российскую
juvenile the queen
молодью the queen у
you have so people for that is she bacchila svetlana
вас так люди на то есть она побачила
dad man people live and you
светлана папа человек люди живут и ты
cool and bachish and eat better with russian you
cool и бачишь и есть краще с русским ты
want mitvol these paints so here we
хочешь митволь вот эти краски так тут у
have batu people came
нас бату людей приехали
to europe so exactly the boss i.e. to
в европу так точно начальник то есть на
work yes i.e. that is business i.e.
работу да то есть то есть бизнес то есть
from the courses we’ll work from yak there and on the right the
из курсов побачим от як там и справа
tenants go there for themselves  so shvydka you are
жильцы туда на себя так швыдкой етесь
culturally economical there, he
культурные там экономичной он и так и
shone the law if he blocks so
сияли закон сувал если ему блоки так он
he feels sorry for him that the prince is like and let's say the
его жаль что царевич якось и скажем
product is a swamp export comfort in
продукту это болото экспорт уют в
natural alabaster poke and these are the
естественных alabaster поки и вот такие
girls I'm boneing the anka archive so basically
девчата я костя архиве анка так принципе
so dota
так dota
e hope natasha ours  people sh still
е надей наташу наш народ sh таки
vile Ustyug on the shaft and just miss each other and
подлая устюг на валу так и разминуться и
look like a
вида
family of European peoples so you can see and
семью европейских народов так видно и
with your head held high glory to Ukraine
с высоко поднятой головой слава украине